export const SEED_STARTER_DECKS = [
        {
            title: 'World Cup Trivia',
            questions: [
                {
                    question: 'Which country won the first ever World Cup?',
                    answer: 'Uruguay, back when it was still called the Jules Rimet Trophy.'
                },
                {
                    question: 'Which country has won the most World Cups?',
                    answer: 'Brazil who have lifted the cup an astonishing five times.'
                },
                {
                    question: 'Who is the all-time highest goalscorer in World Cup history?',
                    answer: 'German striker Miroslav Klose has netted 16 times edging out the likes of Brazil legends Ronaldo and Pele.'
                },
                {
                    question: 'What was the fastest goal scored in World Cup history?',
                    answer: 'Hakan Sukur of Turkey scored against South Korea in 2002 taking just 11 seconds after kickoff.'
                },
            ]
        },
        {
            title: 'Movie Trivia',
            questions: [
                {
                    question: 'What are the top 3 highest nominally grossing films of all-time?',
                    answer: '(1) Avatar (2) Titanic (3) Star Wars: The Force Awakens'
                },
                {
                    question: 'What are the top 3 highest grossing (inflation adjusted) films of all-time?',
                    answer: '(1) Gone with the Wind (2) Avatar (3) Titanic'
                },
                {
                    question: 'What is the all-time record for most Academy Awards for a single film?',
                    answer: 'In all of movie history only 3 movies have ever won 11 Academy Awards: (1) Ben-Hur (1959) (2) Titanic (1997) (3) The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King (2003)'
                },
                {
                    question: 'Which actor has won the most Best Actor Academy Awards?',
                    answer: 'Daniel Day-Lewis has won it an impressive three times.'
                },
                {
                    question: 'Which actress has won the most Best Actress Academy Awards?',
                    answer: 'Katharine Hepburn has a grand total of four Best Actress Awards. No one has been able to imitate her feat to date.'
                },
            ]
        },
        {
            title: 'World Facts Trivia',
            questions: [
                {
                    question: 'What is the largest country in the world by population?',
                    answer: 'China, with India a close second.'
                },
                {
                    question: 'What is the largest country in the world by total area?',
                    answer: 'Russia by a long way if we are just talking countries. Antarctica comes in second but it ain\t a country.'
                },
                {
                    question: 'What is the largest country in the world by GDP?',
                    answer: 'The USA takes the crown here, one they have been holding for awhile now. Japan used to be second for years however China has since taken its place.'
                },
                {
                    question: 'What is the world\'s top tourist destination?',
                    answer: 'France. In 2016 it had a reported 82.6 million international tourist arrivals.'
                },
            ]
        }
]